module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is it called when you combine 2 words like June and Nineteenth?', 
      a: 'Portmanteau', 
      b: 'Kathmandu',
      c: 'Roshambo',
      d: 'Fondu',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year was the first Juneteenth?', 
      a: '1863', 
      b: '1865',
      c: '1866',
      d: '1869',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year was the Emancipation Proclamation issued?', 
      a: '1863', 
      b: '1865',
      c: '1866',
      d: '1869',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What state was the site of the first Juneteenth?', 
      a: 'Ohio', 
      b: 'Virginia',
      c: 'Texas',
      d: 'Pennsylvania',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many people were enslaved in TX in 1865?', 
      a: '100,000', 
      b: '250,000',
      c: '275,000',
      d: '400,000',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What event shortly followed the announcement that slaves were free in TX on Juneteenth?', 
      a: 'The Scatter', 
      b: 'The Diaspora',
      c: 'The Underground Railroad',
      d: 'The Fuck-This-Shit-Im-Out',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What state was the first to declare Juneteenth a state holiday?', 
      a: 'California', 
      b: 'New York',
      c: 'North Carolina',
      d: 'Texas',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year did TX do that :point_up: ?', 
      a: '1865 :better-clap:', 
      b: '1910 :cool-cool-cool: ',
      c: '1965 :meh:',
      d: '1980 :face_with_rolling_eyes:',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is one popular way of celebrating Juneteenth?', 
      a: 'Sipping on red drinks', 
      b: 'Working at your corporate job that wont make it a holiday',
      c: 'Back flips',
      d: 'Screaming into your pillow with unfettered rage that racism still exists in America and around the world',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What will you do to become more educated on Juneteenth and other Black History?', 
      a: 'Google that shit and read', 
      b: 'Watch great docs that center black voices',
      c: 'Not ask my black friends bc its not their job',
      d: 'All of the above :black_heart:',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};